{
    "subject": "resource/WFLZ-FM",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "WFLZ-FM (93.3 FM, \"93-3 FLZ\")  is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA. The station has a class C signal operating at 100,000 watts effective radiated power, and is one of the most powerful FM radio stations in Florida, covering four of the state's radio markets.  The station's studios are located in South Tampa and the transmitter site is in Riverview.WFLZ currently broadcasts in HD format.  93.3 HD-1 simulcasts the analog WFLZ-FM 93.3 MHz (\"93-3 FLZ HD-1 Hit music\"), whereas 93.3 HD-2 exclusively broadcasts dance music (\"Evolution on 93-3 FLZ HD-2\").",
    "human_readable": "WFLZ-FM is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8663392663002014,
            "question": "In what state is WFLZ-FM broadcasting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8254604935646057,
            "question": "Is WFLZ-FM a local or national radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8238275647163391,
            "question": "Where is WFLZ-FM located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6621758341789246,
            "question": "Can you name other radio stations in the Tampa Bay area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5465435981750488,
            "question": "Name three popular artists typically played on CHR/Pop stations."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52649986743927,
            "question": "What type of music does WFLZ-FM play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33704906702041626,
            "question": "How might listening to WFLZ-FM influence someone's musical preferences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32857730984687805,
            "question": "What is the acronym 'CHR/Pop' in relation to music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27666211128234863,
            "question": "What does 'Tampa Bay area' refer to geographically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10043718665838242,
            "question": "What role does radio play in local communities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WFLZ-FM is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4396_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Tampa Bay area' refer to geographically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4396_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the acronym 'CHR/Pop' in relation to music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4396_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might listening to WFLZ-FM influence someone's musical preferences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4396_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4396_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while it is true that WFLZ-FM is a radio station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA (as stated in multiple documents), and it is also mentioned as being a CHR/Pop station (in one document), there is no direct confirmation of this specific format (CHR/Pop) across all the provided documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that WFLZ-FM is a CHR/Pop station broadcasting in the Tampa Bay area, Florida, USA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "information from different parts of the context suggest that WFLZ-FM is a Top 40 radio station, not CHR/Pop.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}